KAYITESI LILIANE

Software developer

Phone: +250791459051 • Email address: Kayitesililiane73@gmail.com GitHub: https://github.com/lilika67|LinkedIn: Kayitesi Liliane

SUMMARY

I am a Dedicated and hardworking individual with a passion for excellence in every task undertaken. I possess exceptional interpersonal skills, fostering positive relationships with colleagues and clients alike. I also demonstrate active listening abilities, ensuring clear understanding and effective communication. I am always committed to delivering results and exceeding expectations in all endeavours. In addition to that I am always open to new experiences and learning new things.

Work Experience

BACKEND TRAINEE SheCanCode Rwanda

Nov 2023-Feb 2024

- Developed a library management system using MERN(MongoDB,Express,ReactJs,NodeJs) to solve the problem of limited education resources experienced by many primary student in Rwanda.
- Developed a stock management system

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER TRAINEE

Andela Rwanda

Feb 2024-Present

- Developed my personal brand using MERN stack(MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, NodeJS)
- Worked together with my team to develop an e-commerce platform which will be helping buyers and sellers to connect so as to make commercial transactions.
- Used PERN stack(Postgress, Express, ReactJs and NodeJs) to develop web projects.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Software engineering

2023-Present

African Leadership University

Certifications

Certified Backend Engineer

2024

Certificate for JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

2013

Professional Skills

- Leadership Skills
- Active-listening skills
- Problem-solving skills
- Critical Thinking
- Communication Skills

Technical Skills

- React Js
- Node Js
- Rest APIs
- Javascript
- Typescript
- MERN StackPERN Stack